

PROFILE

I am a recent graduate with experience in software testing, data analysis and programming. I have a lot of passion for technology and computer science. My main area of interest is automated testing, especially using Python and Selenium.

SKILLS

Python and its libraries and frameworks:

- Flask
- Django
- numpy
- pandas
- pytest
- pytest-bdd/Behave

Selenium Cucumber Java SQL REST

LANGUAGES

English - Advanced, Polish - Native

CERTIFICATES

ISTQB Foundation Level

EMILIA CHOJAK

email: emilia.chojak@gmail.com

mobile: +48 601 522 588

address: Wiśniowa 63/7, 02-520 Warsaw, Poland

GitHub link: github.com/emiliachojak

EDUCATION

University of Warsaw

10.2018 - 07.2020

MSc, Molecular Biotechnology

Maria Curie-Skłodowska University, Lublin

10.2015 - 07.2018

BSc, Biotechnology, Poland 2015 - 2018

EXPERIENCE

CloudBest, Junior Data Analyst

07.2020 - present

I joined a team in Research & Development who work on various new projects utilizing machine learning. My daily tasks involved mostly analysing data, using existing machine learning algorithms to solve various problems, mainly ones related to health and medicine, and working on image processing. I have done most of my coding in Python, including libraries like numpy, pandas, Tensorflow and OpenCV. I was also responsible for doing technical and biomedical research.

Nencki Institute of Experimental Biology, Junior Data Analyst/ Research Assistant

07.2019 - 02.2020

I was a part of a collaborative international research team focused on utilizing AI and computational biology in neuroinformatic study of the structure of primate brains. Main technologies used were: Python, NumPy, SciPy, pandas, scikit-image, ITK-Snap. My main tasks consisted of obtaining AI training data, comparing data generated by AI with data produced by scientists and reporting the differences, manual and automated image processing and creating data visualizations.

WARTA Life Insurance Company

09.2018 - 02.2019

I was a part of a team responsible for testing manually existing and new parts of a big national insurance system. My main tasks consisted of executing manual tests based on prepared test cases and scenarios, reporting bugs, writing test cases and writing simple SQL queries.